what up
I'm going to just link to this end
escort
it's not worth tweeting about you guys
you guys know the discord let's go right
here give a little bit of time for some
people to get in here I got two things
to show you today it's gonna be quick
livestream what's up walks or hello
Logan Legrand welcome everybody
close the doors my office take off her
hoodie welcome welcome welcome so we
have one question to ask today and
that's our FCA people better than Subaru
people so wait why is this not here
let's see is it live oh yes it is
oh-ho FCA car honest if you right now go
to our shop you can buy one of these
guys this is a harness it supports we're
gonna go through all the cars that it
supports it supports the chrysler
pacifica it supports the chrysler
pacifica Hybrid all of the user
supported but you know things like this
this is the bosch one I'm sorry tonight
I've fun um and then where's the Jeep at
yeah it also supports the Jeep Grand
Cherokee so you can buy you can buy an
FCA harness put this in your chrysler
pacifica and be just like way mom you
can you can you can be just like lame-o
um it's not more carports what we're
doing is we're consolidating everything
a comma is about stability is about ease
of use is about making this stuff
consumer friendly that's the word
consumer friendly that's right so it's
very easy for you to install this it's
completely behind the trim this is the
first harness we've had to do can you
buy a car with Eon on it no we don't
sell cars
is the first harness we've had to do a
little bit differently so you see these
ones are just straight-up wire harnesses
unfortunately the female FCA connector
and actually we should make sure let's
make sure just the harness connector
connector perfect you can buy se a
harness connectors to only $50 this is
really in the same deal because it
includes two parts it includes both this
wiring harness part and this little
adapter board which goes from this what
is that 12 pin molex to this FC a female
and you see the FC a female fits into
the FCA male beautifully can you buy a
car and put Eon in it then sell me no no
no no no this isn't for you man this
isn't for you this is a chill livestream
what I'm gonna tweet about it no tweet
about the livestream it's chill just for
the discord grows we got something else
to show you too but we're only gonna
show to you if at least one person buys
the FC a harness we need one person oh
you know what we're gonna we're gonna
add everyone maybe they will just do in
the announcements Channel FCA
artis is live
you want to try open pilot is there any
help no there's not any help there's no
help no there's help you can come on
this cord but if you're not technical
it's not for you when you can try right
but but open I'll just give and take
right open pile it's not just like if
you think you're gonna like buy like an
Apple watch and just install it not
another no but if you're willing to put
the time in you get something before
everybody else in the world like this
beautiful FCI harness so we just need to
wait for a few people to get in here we
need to sell one of these it's gonna get
easier it's always gonna get easier but
you know if you're asking those kind of
questions those are all kind of
questions there's always help hop on
disk fci harness is live and we're at
the kebab shop now another thing kebab
Shepherd is right around the corner
though makes great kebabs FCA harness
there isn't really that much more to say
about it we also fire tweet today
exactly yeah somebody sent them an
overpriced car that sounds like the
right solution here 40 more people come
one come all to this absolutely chill
don't tweet about it stream where we
launched the FCI harness and we figure
out once and for all if FCA people are
better than Subaru people all right
maybe when we get to 50 people I'll show
you guys the cool thing so let's talk
about upcoming features I know new
features ever that's right all features
are canceled that's a lie we launched
the MCA harness the Hyundai harness
coming soon and if you want to get one
of these FCA harnesses you got three
days you got three days to come down to
our virtual store at shop comedy eye and
buy it if you want to get it fulfilled
before the holiday break give your loved
one hours of entertainment buy them an
eon of what this does is it allows you
to plug in your chrysler pacifica or
your jeep compass I think we also
support one more car
soon to yem like maps yeah no no maps
are never gonna have maps a lie
you see we've updated the readme we've
included limitations be sure to read
these very carefully like you read your
car owner manual and we push some cars
into community maintain cars and
features but fortunately the Chrysler's
are right here in officially supported
cars the jeeps are right here and
officially supported car things because
actually a lot more to get what you mean
red lights and stop signs like this like
whoa is that is that open pilot running
on on a PC look at that model detecting
that lane look at that oh yeah we
support Kia Kia's are just you and eyes
yeah open pilot in simulation you want
to talk about features look at that this
is just a computer that's manager
running entirely on a computer will fix
the slow frame thing this is real this
is very real um this is Karla so uh yeah
yeah we're gonna make open pilot run in
well it's an internal fork for now but
we're gonna make open pilot run in
simulation this is a big push for next
year so everybody can develop with open
pilot not just people who have the
supported cars we got some absolutely
crazy announcements lined up for 2020
FCA harnesses are just the start do we
need a do you need a GPU there's one in
the CPU right now not kind of runs on
the CPU we got we got some great reuse
some great research from from from the
research team let's see if we sell any
FCA harnesses you know the amount of
leaks that I want to give has a lot to
do with how much FCA harnesses we sell
and so far there's been zero FCA harness
is stalled so we got I'll show you and I
never want to show you user stuff but
that's what's happening with our store
today so you know we got to get this
number we got to get this number up we
got to go way way up
open pilot unfortunately we can't move
yet oh if you already have the hub um if
you've already bought the harness you
can go right in here and you can just
buy the harness connector we sell them
for $50 Subaru is right now equivalent
to FCA nobody bought any Subaru
harnesses either I think we filled six
of them so far but I believe in you FTA
people come by come by FCA yeah look it
simulation all right all right your your
yurt no no no this is the wrong kind of
questions to ask I don't know if it's
legal I'm not a lawyer man you got it
you got it you got to ask your friendly
neighborhood lawyer about that
FCA harness buy it right now $50 if you
want the black panda which you
definitely do want the black Panda yeah
simulated car that's that's what I'm
talking about
can I Drive a simulated car I'm not sure
I don't think I wrote any of that maybe
we can do a coding livestream later
where we write some of that code but um
whoa whoa
oh no I thought we got an order I got
excited about the forbidden topic if
it's demonstratively safe and time
there's a lot of forbidden topics I'll
let you mention one word event which
which which forbidden topic if it's
torque interceptors no oh don't know
okay look
torque interceptors look there's less
safe things in the world than to work
interceptors if you truly have built a
torque interceptor that is as LD and
applies the limits and meets all
automotive standards I think you can
build a safe torque interceptor but I
think that the the
to do it is really beyond a hobbyist
project so if you guys are like a
company and you're building torque
interceptors and like you know you've
put a lot of resources into Q&A into
testing then I do think torque
interceptors are possible but I think
that an open-source torque interceptor
like the way the pedal is open-source is
extremely dangerous this is the worst
case law if your pedal freaks out the
worst thing that happens is your car you
get uncontrollable acceleration well go
into neutral step on the brake you're
fine
uncontrollable steering torque that's
Azal v yeah you gotta you know commas
for people who are gonna who are gonna
search and find come on FTA people can
we sell one of these things you guys
make me never want to introduce new
harnesses you guys make me realize that
the only car anybody cares about is
Honda's in Toyotas um you think some of
it can be deconstructed to be given the
control method how and what do you mean
by deconstructed if you're straight-up
intercepting the torque sensor on power
steering I don't see how that's not D
because of malfunction you're thinking
cause ah beautiful
all right we got four visitors right now
on the store I don't see the live view
or any you guys buying in FCI harness I
just want I just want to conclude this
video with the conclusion that FCA
people are better than Subaru people and
we can leave it there oh oh we got we
got a person there where are these other
visitors
since it's harder to control the motor
it's less likely for a catastrophic
failure you know what how about this
before you post a safety analysis post
like an ISO 266 to safety analysis of a
torque interceptor and we're happy to
comment on it
this isn't about remote control why is
remote control is absolutely banned
what what what what could you possibly
be doing good with remote control at
least a torque interceptor like torque
interceptors have positive value too
right yeah flexing exactly thumbs down
thumbs down right
well we gave up safety so we could flex
thumbs down even once a dog ran right
0:06 visitors right now oh oh oh come on
come on somebody buy one somebody buy
one oh you know you want to buy one
they're beautiful they're they're FCA
harnesses they're only $50 399 when
coupled with a brand-new black panda
that has integrated GPS I don't have one
of my desk all I have is on my desk is
an e on up oh boy what a gem cell what
do we just sell was that an SCA - I'm
gonna check I'm gonna check
up oh yeah if you announce your name on
the stream I will confirm that it was
you who purchased an FBI harness thank
you we have absolutely proven that FCA
people are better than super people
thank you for buying you guys give me
hope you guys give me hope of launching
harnesses now spill okay okay okay you
want a leak will show you a leak this is
the research teams leak but let me see
if I can find it okay what no no no what
oh no I don't know anything about it oh
no we don't have any works um but we do
have this joint model oh yes oh this see
these end-to-end longitudinal you see
this integrated pose net yeah and you
see how the curves are beautifully
sloping down the models the deep is
learning oh it's beautiful oh look at
that
yeah come the other leak which I'm sure
many you guys have already found is um
it's not so hard to enable automatic
lane changes but we haven't officially
shipped automatically and changes its
not shipped and do remember that the
automatic lane change does not respect
the blind spot so that is always your
job it's good enough the problem with
red lights and stop signs is not the
camera red lights and stop signs are
hard for a whole different set of
reasons but this stuff man end-to-end
longitudinal control
that's one of the things I'm really
excited for in 2020 in addition you guys
have seen hopefully in zero 7 vo ATC I
think well it's no radar right so in
zero six two we switched I know 2020 is
near vests right um in zero six two we
switched from the radar being the
primary sensor to vision being the
primary sensor um you tried to take the
lane changes to a curb and it was ready
to go it'll tell you yeah if you turn
the blinker on it'll still tell you um
it shouldn't actually make the lane
change but again that feature is not
officially shipped we did leave the
skeleton in there for it so you guys can
can can mess around and start
experimenting with it was the biggest
harness purchase we sold a lot I think I
think Taiwan there's a bunch of people
in Taiwan really buy a lot of these
things in big quantities we get another
FC a harness or am I being too greedy
it's really a beautiful harness comes
with these tiny boards reading the speed
limit signs again these sound like
community features community features
you guys can write that stuff um we've
open-sourced like all of open pilot is
open source now it should be relatively
easy for you guys to add a something
else that runs the model bro shop is
slow take a look you're this close to
getting banned I don't know what to tell
you man you use dial-up does it make
does it make a mean noise when you
connect to the internet well maybe
that's why it's long huh
what else we got when is autopilot when
is open file for PC gonna be released
what has been my pet project sometime in
in 2020 San Diego is a beautiful place
you know they say it's always sunny in
philadelphia this ally I've been to
Philadelphia but San Diego is pretty
close when open pilot for the Xbox 360
Oh way better in the Bay Area yes we
sell one more FCA harness what's our B
because they're really really a lot
about our B oh oh well should we make
fun of should we make fun of startups
briefly our B is the first company oh
wow that's slow welcome to radars new
era our B is disrupting radar technology
to support drivers and autonomous
vehicles
Zook says let's just say I haven't seen
the other 500 million of their around to
come through all oh it uses 4d imaging
radar oh I can trust it oh that's all
that's good to know that's good to know
man you know when I go on Bosh's website
they call it the radar you can't trust
that's not even my side I'm glad you
like the lane change ooh
proprietary chipset technologies this is
a joke is this I don't know if this is
at all or not I don't know hopefully you
guys the new manager status line I wrote
this myself it's green and it's red when
the processes crash yeah I took typed
out those anti codes yeah what else just
make sure I'm not oh oh do we have any
more orders or someone else want to buy
one there they're really beautiful the
FCA harness is a wonderful harness it's
like if juice arrow made a radar that
sounds about right
how hard is it to add car simulation
it's pretty easy
headless the headless Aeon stuff is not
gonna go anywhere the problem with the
headless Eon stuff is first it only
works on one car and second you're
limited by the features that are being
outputted by the stock camera the
features are not very good it's not
taking a picture from the camera you
can't do that you're just using you know
Bosh's crappy lame finding algorithms
and then like making guesses based on
that which is really not the way to
build one of these things
so always good to see people
experimenting but I don't think that
that is very fertile I think what would
be more fruitful and what you can
experiment if you insist to use
something that's not like the ER mounted
on the screen is you could probably get
open pilot working pretty well with a
webcam um my long-term goals not
headless Obama does kind of annoy us
yeah we we we ship eons and we'll ship
better eons and the Nubians will be you
know slimmer and smaller and have more
cameras so on and so forth and you know
for the next for the next Eon years but
um you know headless is not headless is
not a goal well let me show you the ads
where would we show you the ads that's
the question all right 65 feet we got
anything else
thank you speed drawing 101 wanna pee on
the cars compute not really I mean I was
making fun of the car people for not
putting any real computers in their car
if they're a real computer sure maybe us
running on an iPhone that's gonna take
you a lot waffle makers still there
well I ship bumper stickers what we're
thinking about bumper stickers like this
car runs open-source software something
like that what you guys think what's for
the bumper sticker say um but no we
don't serve any bumper stickers right
now I think we include some stickers I
think we have some stickers but you know
went out the swag business we're in the
high quality hardware business harness
is one of the highest quality things
coming I was ever shipped so make sure
to buy your harness today I can't show
you that one cuz it has user info
I prefer open pilot disengagement
instead of Tesla autopilot yeah gasps
disengagement makes so much sense how
long will the current Aeon be around
eons Pan know you'll say I mean you'll
see all in 2020 all in 2020 things will
happen
see look if we had new heart if we had
if we had new hardware right around the
corner what I have a neon on my desk the
way man um all right so FCA people are
slightly better than Subaru people true
the been determined
we're gonna go for uh what is Lou I
don't know anything about you know um uh
yeah the dash cam the dash cams got
really good your if you guys have comic
prime um try out the comic connect app
has gotten quite good in the last
release I show us a neon in a test card
yeah we can we can we can go it can go
now when I got to do that that's a long
walk um Opie long end-to-end
longitudinal control 2020 that's really
gotten good you know we debated in 0-7
all the videos the videos are quick yeah
right hey I know the quality is not that
great but that's the trade-off those
videos are small enough that they can
keep up live on comm prime so if you are
comma prime subscriber those videos will
show up in your phone almost instantly
from your drive um it truly is a cloud
dash cam okay we'll let you in on one
more thing this isn't finalized yet
right now if you're a normal comma user
you got three days of storage comma
prime gets 14 days of storage we're
thinking about increasing that to one
year comma prime is about to be really
good you know we put a lot of effort
into it those features in tell you about
internal debates
I like internal to comma there's no
debate I'm a dictator
not show a lot of talking about
fingerprinting 2.0 a lot of debates on
how we're gonna do that what else know
come from is not free it's $24 a month
bro we debated on how much comma crime
should cost let me tell you something
everybody else in the company they want
to make things cheap for you guys and
I'm like no no nothing no no no we got
to make it expensive so whatever
something's expensive I'm the guy to
blame are we hiring any developers we
are we are we're hiring an open pilot
engineer somebody who's good really
infrastructure testing a lot of that
stuff if you're good with we were
talking today like if you like if you
don't C++ you're on the right track but
also maybe hiring an ml engineer maybe
if you're very very good but open pilot
engineer will hire you tomorrow if you
uh if you are if you do great boxer if
you're looking for a job
um C++ is it's a language yeah yeah how
do we stop progressions in the models oh
we have all these complicated we have
lots of we have lots of tests maybe
someday we'll go live to the to the
research team and the research team know
we don't charge money for album pod by
prime um I don't feel good
look I'm not the kind of guy who's gonna
charge you money for a software that
runs on your device you bought and paid
for an e-1 from us I'm not gonna charge
you to use your device I'm not one of
those dicks right we do charge you of
course
jeez comma Prime come front cost us
money over an MVNO we we resell a
certain large mobile carrier service to
you guys and we have to pay that mobile
carrier money on the back end so that's
you know come front cost us money coming
from all so honestly honestly we don't
even make money on comic prime because
the azure bill is so high yo
gotta pay for cloud now whoa whoa whoa
wait when I was a page me that wasn't a
sale come on come on FCA people buy some
harnesses we got we got we got two more
minutes
Alton media I didn't say that I'm just
saying I didn't say that aloud uh-huh
yeah clouds for users data like videos
yeah yeah we got we got videos in the
cloud
it's like Pied Piper but only for
dashcam videos and we're really we're
thinking about increasing it to one year
no promises on that there's still
internal debate um you know you know see
people are like oh you know I want to
work serious like man we want to give
all the people great features and I come
along and I'm like does that cost money
they're not gonna cost money sounds like
it's gonna cost money no not a no it's
gotta go we make money we're almost
profitable to uh Q for this Q for is our
highest profit quarter on record already
um and if we it's already let's let's
let me let me get you the total I'll let
you in on the total let's go quarter
today let me make sure there's no user
information here yes this is commas most
profitable quarter today and why don't I
show you guys this stuff I think I'm
crazy
um yeah man three hundred ninety seven
thousand dollars that is almost a
profitable company our burn rates about
I'm gonna mount one eighty a month um so
so we're we're we're seventy eighty
percent of the way to profitable I'm
very happy we're up 43 percent from the
last quarter which was a new record
quarter four comma we're really we're
really killing it and wait'll you guys
see what we haven't done we're gonna
blow you away in 2020 right if you think
if you think what we've done so far if
you thought this year was a good year
wait'll you see the lineup for 2020
things have been working no hockey stick
growth not real yawns don't use the
microphone how many eons are out there
driving here looking rid of bad
information
no we're not at when not at 5k monthly
users yet I'd like to get there let me
just
it's an overview I'll bring up weekly
for the last six months it takes a while
to load it's got a hit on my sequel
database ah no no no prime is all stored
and then Prime is all stored measure
there we go here's the weekly devices
chart
so that's ignore the last couple weeks
aren't up to date it takes a bit for
things to actually like make their way
into the system but yeah so we've
reached a bit over 1100 weekly active
users and you see our growth is nice and
steady um you know if you guys didn't
read my medium posts you guys should be
concise comedy i we just kind of break
down what do you do it's like Facebook
is like my sequel they focus back below
is what I worked there was backed by big
my single database I don't know no then
you put memcache in front of it and
there you go
the harness videos current Eon uses a
phone you can't get anymore
what do you mean there well oh you want
me to jog I know but um ya know if you
guys didn't read didn't read this
breaking down unit economics this is our
monthly device growth should we've
really does that's just been in two
years and you can see this is actually a
slight upward exponential to that to so
you know hockey sticks girl it's not
real but exponential growth is yeah this
is if you guys didn't read this go read
it we're not even gonna make fun of
startups anymore comma
hires full-time we only hire on-site yes
you think I'm dealing with managing a
bunch of contractors come here because
you want to add value if you make a GM
harness we're thinking about it
tamo coins not real never gonna happen
we'll be doing constant hardware versus
a on versus a phone tell me what
improvements there are to make I think
there's one big improvement but I think
that you'll you'll actually find I don't
think winstram AIC today I think you'll
actually find that that improvement can
be made very easily with a phone as well
cool be consumer ready well you know
we're at 0.7 we got 0.8 we got 0.9 we
got 1.0 we into a stream for 0.7 but it
is pretty cool driver monitoring at
night yeah no one's interesting to the
night driver monitoring and uh no
battery and permanent install well uh
you know 2020 guy's 2020 you'll see uno
this dog Luna who's not real
who told you about who no um yeah you
guys get yawns man beyond this where it
is gonna be at sea yeah so told you that
who knows and I did huh oh yeah know who
know is uh no no it's just it's for the
Spanish market
yeah it's yawns for the Spanish market
yeah the comic you know yeah that's
right we got that we got it we got a you
know we're right down we're right next
to Iran San Diego is well it's much
better than San Francisco in New York um
let's just say yeah the como uno is the
the EON for the market we're right next
to Mexico you know we're gonna get a lot
of Tijuana sales so the comic uno
what does Tesla have that we don't what
tests the feature do you like that we
don't have right now I can think of a
big feature we have the Tesla doesn't
have make it funny you on for this
morning
oh yeah that's right that's right Thank
You Go Go quiero mucho dinero por , no
uh some people on Hacker News felt that
I'm dismissive of marketing yeah yeah
why would I want to market marketing you
know think I'm who clicks ads alright I
just do you think smart people click ads
what do you think dumb people click at
right and now think you think marketing
is a good idea
oh well come I have a booth at CES ah
not to hear anything about that I don't
know we can ask around that I don't know
um I want to launch a new Aeon three or
four cameras why do you need more
cameras explain to me what you're gonna
do with more cameras all common dos o BM
W no no flex right exactly you have an
ad blocker see even you want to sleep
alone has an ad blocker hey um what's
the state of the industry it's all total
dog man but you know it's not even
fun anymore right like it used to be fun
when we were punching up when we were
like this small startup struggling to
survive or punch it the big startups
like it was fun but like now it's like
you know it's not uh it's not funny
anymore right like like Zuke's actually
can't raise their money alright like
it's just it's just sad
yo how about this you buy me a banners
truck and I'll work hard to port it man
I'll try to do that pour myself I'll
pour it to the been stuff will get to me
on an adventure
alright can we sell anymore FCA or
nicest we're sold we sold we sold one
so one I'll take it you guys are one
better than then does Subaru any more
questions I said what
how is Christmas in our office I said to
get a Christmas tree I don't think
anyone actually did it I was doing good
21 yeah uh forward lock out bro email
for I don't know I can't believe I
bought that car well I lost like ten
grand on that cart oh they depreciate so
fast so disappointed really Honda and
more importantly Toyota Toyota is really
where it's at buy a Corolla next year
you're here yo uh no actually check it
out we launched a new uh oh don't get me
started on how much I lost on the ct6 we
launched a new compatibility flow it's
really nice and here we have compatible
cars we recommend really really get at
that Corolla but these are all nice cars
you'll work with my I'd say my Porsche
911 2019 oh no that's too bad
yeah Corolla should be at the top we
should change that yeah I know the
website super fast I know but some
people on dial-up rav4 is very good yeah
TSS 2 is better than all Honda's the
rav4 is very good
the we do recommend the round 4 right
yeah we do yeah the TSS 2 rav4 is great
the curl is really the best car you got
so much torque on that thing
great car pick up a Corolla and while
you're at it by a neon and Toyota bona
bundle right now buy it um Thursday so
let's just bring up a calendar and 2019
December let me just bring one of these
up so you can see yeah we support all
praises the 19th is our last day that
we're doing fulfillment so if you want
to get your order in
uh no Ford is over you guys Vivienne's
the only Ford we have here this Ford is
over no Ford uh no I don't know if
someone supports Ford we top stream it I
think we already released the code that
we wrote for it oh yeah look at that
look at that look at that look at the
line look at how nice is detecting that
line that's a solid model we don't have
driver monitoring on pc yea thou coming
soon ah EPS record oh no no no we don't
want any we're not doing any firmware no
no no no firmware hacks no firmware
hacks people externally do though hey
you know that's on you if done if done
properly we don't think they're
dangerous
if Opie malfunctions how hard is it to
overpower the car so what do you mean by
that
right open pilot it can't put you can
combat the torque open pilot can put on
the wheel I used to say with a pinkie
but in the Corolla it might take these
two fingers ah but still if you have a
hand on the wheel there is no way open
pilot can overpower you if you if you
have a hand like gripping the wheel
you'll see them a maximum amount of work
it can put it so much less than you can
so if you're worried about that you can
check we we have we have the safety code
in pan if it's not even our safety code
we're that's really just using the
safety code of the car um we're using
the same interface that the car cameras
are using
well does it need to be these two
fingers when I like you know the good
fingers are nice for you know pushing
back on things you could use these two
but it'd be kind of like awkward you
know what were we talking about before
that oh yeah yeah we released also check
our medium we did a nice tour through
open pilot this is pretty good good
just engagements are going down I don't
really have clean data to share it's a
hard thing to measure it's it's uh no no
no we're not to his thought up preview I
can honestly guys I just feel bad for
people in this space I feel bad
it's like LeBron going to a high school
and dunking on the high school team
that's what it's like no no they're not
it's not even it's not even that it's
like it's like the Jacksonville Jaguars
man it's like it's like when Bill
Belichick beats the Jacksonville Jaguars
all right that's that's what I'm saying
um
ya know it's it's getting a lot better
what's going on please explain well
launching the FC a harness this guy plug
it into your FC a Yeti you know what's
sad I'll show you something sad everyone
at comma was really happy about that
that AV analysis post you know we all
thought it was cool and then like here's
the truth so we come out with the AE B
we get 247 claps I write a poorly
thought out post shit-talking other
companies and we get two point one
thousand claps right so like this is
probably one of the best things like
like like this is a really unique thing
that only comic can do we analyzed
millions of miles and we looked for all
I II be events definitely worth reading
247 claps
and that's the problem you got to give
the people what they want thank you I'm
glad you appreciate it
we're still waiting at this traffic
light we got to engage open pilot let's
engage I want to refactor so you can see
this is actually this is just UI this is
like UI dot C it's the same one that
runs in the computer I want to refactor
the background to be here
we'll get the vault man glad I'm glad
you read it um
I want to add like all the settings
stuff to here we'll take all that out of
Android that should give us some more
CPU performance launching message queue
that's gonna get a similar CPU
performance there's so much performance
to still be added to the Aeon there's so
much performance we can squeeze out of
that thing Linux Linux alright 45
minutes I had 90 more seconds we sold
one Fc a harness that's one more than we
sold Subaru harnesses I trust that
they're gonna trickle and slowly over
time one-year storage yeah yes order of
magnitude I I think the one year is
gonna happen
performance equals more steering if you
want more steering just buy a Toyota
Corolla it has all the steer and you
ever wanted
outtie howdy is the same as VW for some
outies the ones that use flex ray is not
gonna happen there are there are people
on discord hacking away at flex right
maybe they'll make some progress but um
it seems it seems really complex we have
a lot we have internal data analysis on
driver monitoring maybe well maybe we'll
do one of those public right we'll put
it together performance equals more
Headroom I mean you know we got more
Headroom LED on those new models that I
showed you guys they're huge
you good models for X bigger than the
current models and that doesn't even
make the Box bigger yet we're gonna make
the Box bigger as well
I will not for EXO cuz we're reading
that 18 to a resident 50 so you know
real deep learning models resna 50s or
what uh opening I used
you can use it young on a Tesla yes you
can come asking discord on the Tesla
channel whoo guys thank you all for
joining today I'm glad to have you all
here this has been coming on she's
probably gonna be our last livestream
for 2019 no Christmas gift we're gonna
really start 2020 off with a bang and I
think it's gonna be good see you in 20